Light's up, crowd up, this is me
And tonight we open the gates to the topia
Three days, three nights
We rise under these first-to-all lines
Stepping, filled with beat
The Toby is here, your heart's new heat
Are you ready to move? Are you ready to shine?
Beep, so be begins, right now in line line line line
Beep, oh be up, let the bass hit shine
Beep, oh be up, let the night lift
Just and booby, big sound, booby, to the ground
Beep, oh be up, hear me
Beep, oh be up weschau be up
Beep, oh be up, up we are
Beep, hey, shou, shou, cus, shou, uh
Beep, so beer, beehah, dieout lad
Hands up, never come down
You face
Who lies this ground is alive
Three days of fire, three days of dreams
Spook tonight we become
One festival team
O-P-Hop
Turn the whole world up
Let the whole ground jump
The little rain finds the way
It's O-P-Hop
O-P-Hop
This is day one, this is your run
Welcome to V-2-V-A
Let the light be again
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Come on, come on, come on
Hey, hey, hey, hey
Come on, come on
Hands up, never come down